# Jeffrey de Mesa

# Designer and Web Developer

# CONTACT

#### **PHONE**

+6390 8400 4955

## **EMAIL ADDRESS**

jeffdemesa96@gmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

#### **RIZAL TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY**

BS in Information and Communications Technology SY: 2012 - 2017

#### **RIZAL HIGH SCHOOL**

Secondary School SY: 2008 - 2012

# STAR OF HOPE CHRISTIAN SCHOOL

Primary School SY: 2002 - 2008

# **SKILLS**

# INDUSTRY APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

















# **PROTOTYPING & DESIGN TOOLS**









#### **DATABASE APPLICATIONS**





# **STATEMENT**

I am a developer and a designer with a 7+ years of experience in creating user experience designs, mockups, high-fidelity prototypes, and working user interface application. I am also taking a path on backend stuff to have a grasp to build application from both ends.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Sulzer Inc. / September 2022 - September 2023 • 1 year

Development responsibilities that I hold:

- WordPressTheme
- Gutenberg Blocks
- PHP backend
- Different email provider theme development (Mailchimp, Pardot, HubSpot, etc)
- Maintenance of existing websites.

### SENIOR WEB ENGINEER AND DESIGNER

Taxumo / August 2017 - May 2023 • 6 years+

I am responsible for the following:

- user interface design
- database management
- feature development
- RESTful APIs development
- C# backend

Responsible also for the maintenance of web application of Taxumo. I make sure that they have their user has the best experience on overall usability of the app.

### FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER AND DESIGNER

Freelance / August 2016 - Present • 7 years+

I do some freelance projects from various clients in my spare time mostly after my morning shift job. I do some UI designs, mockups, high-fidelity prototypes, web application developments, and WordPress.

# FREELANCE WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Tribe Limited / April 2017 - August 2017 • 5mos

I engage to a wordpress website development contract to this company. I also perform periodic maintenance to which is availed as another contract after the project development.